Tell me about your three arms hahahahaha To tell the truth, which man and woman I like to go out with do not hang out with
講你嘅三懷俾我知 哈哈哈哈 講真 我鍾意同邊個男女出街 咪同邊個男
Girls go out we break up fix me your pervert fix me your sister locks really all the time
女 出街囉 我哋分手 整我你嘅變 態佬 整我你嘅妹鎖呀 真係下下都
It's not serious enough to hurt you or hurt you
傷 害你 你都唔夠重呀
Potato Party Game heard me say the more I play you the better guy right Yeah
薯 記Party Game 聽到 我話 越玩你越正佬喎 Yeah
Well since the sixth anniversary of our Little Potatoes is coming up in September is possible,
好 啦 由於我哋小薯記六周年喇 嚟緊係九月會喺 既可能喇,
We are all you devils.
我們係既各位既魔鬼既既既既既既既 既既既既既既既既既既既既既既既既
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes.
既 既既既既既既既既既既既既既既 既既.
Both 6th Anniversary Pari Time Show!
既既6周年 Pari Time既 Show!
So our platoon is busy rehearsing.
所以呢我地呢排都忙緊彩排啦。
that's right.
冇錯。
This episode of the Party Game will play 3 mini-games about the theater.
今集既Party Game係會玩 3個關於劇場既小遊戲㗎。
And our country today is going to be conducted in the form of an individual match.
而且我地今日係會用個人賽既形式嚟 進行呀。
Ah J, you don't have to be afraid this time, no one will talk to you.
阿J,今次你唔使驚,冇人捋你喇。
You can rely on yourself and win it back...
你可以靠自己,贏返嚟喇.
Everyone depends on their own...
大家都靠自己嘅.
Let's introduce it first, shall we?
我哋介紹下先啦,好唔好?
Who are you?
你邊位呀?
Hello everyone, my name is Aladdin.
大家好,我係阿拉丁.
You are a horse!
你係馬騮!
Awa.
阿波.
No, but I didn't know the OV was a little like Apo, I was interested.
唔係呀,但我都唔知個OV有少少似 阿波,我都性慨嘅.
I wear vinyl...
我係黑膠...
Prince.
太子.
Prince?
太子?
Wrong in the streets...
錯晒喺街頭.
It is sweet and juicy.
佢有甜又多汁㗎.
I am the butterfly of 144P who can't help it.
我就係144P嘅蝴蝶忍唔住.
I can't help but beat you up.
忍唔住打爆你.
Wow!
嘩!
144P.I'm Robin who robbed people of pants products...
144P. 我係劫人褲製品嘅羅賓 ...
Kangkang.
康康.
I thought you were the Green Warrior Tim.
我以為你係綠武俠添.
I can't help it.
我忍唔住啦.
I am Ninja Rentaro.
我係忍者戀太郎呀.
are you a newbie or who
你係新丁定邊個呀?
You really have the same 100% courage as the theme song...
你真係同首主題曲一樣,100%勇 氣呀.
Wow!
嘩!
So pretty.
好靚呀.
introduce.
介紹下.
Hello everyone, I’m Bonnie’s grandma, Dali.
大家好呀,我係Bonnie阿媽臭 大理呀.
I am the same sister.
同姐呀我係.
Sister!
同姐!
I've even stunk you.
我都臭過曬你地呀.
Have you ever stinked me?
你臭過曬我呢?
Hi everyone, I love nature...
大家好呀,我係熱愛大自然嘅...
The People's Congress is deploying troops.
人大安兵呀.
Young people, how do you dress up like that?
年青人,有乜時打扮到咁呀?
Is it my responsibility?
係我定責任呀?
It’s a bear!
係熊呀!
Give you a like!
嗌你個like呀!
Have you never seen Ji Guang, a real man?
未見過濟光真漢子呀?
So domineering.
好霸氣呀.
Ok, let’s get into the first game right away.
好,我哋即刻進入第一個遊戲.
The first rule of the game.
第一遊戲規則.
123 It's Party Time.
123 It's Party Time.
The gameplay is similar to 123 Traffic Light.
玩法類似123紅綠燈.
The host speaks the topic and slogan with his back to the participants.
主持背向參加者講出題目同口號.
Participants need to make the corresponding action at the end of the slogan...
參加者需要喺口號完結時做出相應嘅 動作.
1 point is awarded for successfully crossing the finish line.
成功跨過終點線可得1分.
Okay, read the rules of the game...
好喇,睇完遊戲規則喇.
This game tests everyone's reaction and flexibility...
呢個遊戲就考大家嘅反應同靈活度 嘅.
So flexible.
好靈活呀.
first question.
第一題.
Put on your most MK posture...
擺一個你最MK嘅姿態.
123 It's Party Time.
123 It's Party Time.
A J.
阿J.
OK.
OK.
What’s the solution?
咩料解?
Do you think you are so bad?
識吓你個樣好衰?
I have never seen a blessed disciple when I was pregnant with the sea court...
懷過海庭,我冇見過福徒呀.
Like come, like come.
好似嚟,好似嚟.
To find him?
要搵佢?
ah.
呀.
Oh, that’s right.
噢,咁啱.
OK.
OK.
This MOOK is the best.
呢個MOOK最好呀.
Eat two.
食兩支呀.
I was picking up photos in the toilet...
我喺廁所拎緊相.
Those sticker photos those machines...
嗰啲貼紙相嗰啲機呀.
Okay, second question.
好,第二題.
Classic character action.
經典角色動作.
123 It's Party Time.
123 It's Party Time.
OK.
OK.
This is over.
呢個係過咗喇.
Is it Mia?
係咪呀?
bluebird.
青鳥.
Soski.
索斯基.
Red pig.
紅豬.
No
唔係呀.
What is it?
係咩呀?
Aaron in this street fighter...
呢個街霸裏面嘅阿龍呀.
Wave fist.
波動拳呀.
Sigh.
嘆字郎呀.
OK.
OK.
Master.
Master.
I want to say, confront you.
我想講,對峙呀你.
It doesn't look like a mirror...
又唔似乜鏡呀.
Tutu will find out.
突突會發現身呀.
Why do I suddenly notice my body?
點解我都係突突會發現身嘅?
That's right, you guys wait for you more...
都係喇,你哋等俾你多.
Question three.
第三題.
animal.
動物.
123 It's Party Time.
123 It's Party Time.
I think two to eliminate...
我覺得兩個要淘汰嘅.
One is for you and the other is for Jay.
一個係你,一個係Jay.
what are you
你介係咩嚟㗎?
frog.
青蛙.
My name is Baron.
我係Baron.
Playing with a dog will bring you back the peach.
玩到隻狗係返桃呀.
So what are these two eliminated?
咁呢兩個淘汰咩?
No, what?
唔 係 咩?
But he seems to.
但係佢好似.
OK.
OK.
what are you
你係咩呢㗎?
I'm a dinosaur of plastic...
我係甩膠嘅恐龍呀.
you two are the same
你兩個一樣嘅.
are you again
你又係呀?
I don't have a plastic dinosaur...
我冇甩膠嘅恐龍.
What are you talking about?
呢個咩呢話?
Wood-gnawing dinosaur.
咬柴恐龍。
The dinosaur's hands were like this, but he was accidentally eating grass so he called November.
恐龍嘅手咁樣咁樣,但佢唔小心食緊 草咁佢就叫 November.
Yeah yeah yeah!
呀 呀呀呀!
He said grass-eating dragons, we are obviously tyrannosaurs...
佢話草食龍,我哋好明顯係暴龍嚟 呀.
We are dinosaurs like hands...
我哋做手咁地恐龍.
Herbivorous dragon's hands must not be like this...
草食龍嘅手一定唔會係咁.
It's so obvious, it's so easy to eat.
好明顯咋,食緊草呀.
What are you talking about?
你係咩呢話?
What do you think it is?
你地覺得係咩料啊?
Will there be some little Velociraptors in those groups of ours?
我哋嗰啲群體會唔會有啲小速龍呢?
Are there so many dragons?
咁多龍咩呢?
It's all dragons...
全部都係龍咋喇.
I don't know if I'm right, we have to know what you mean...
唔知去講中咗,大家要唔知好意思係 咩喇.
Question 4, the most bold posture, 1 2 3.
第四題,最露膽既姿勢,1 2 3.
Very skateboarding right that said.
好滑板喎呢個話。
Let me explain first.
你解釋起我先喇.
This is John.
呢個係阿John.
Thank you, but you're back, you're in charge...
唔該曬你,但你返埋後面喇, 你保養喇.
You stop!
你停!
What kind of material is this?
呢個係咩料啊?
What do you think it is?
你覺得係咩料啊?
Where do you want to hit me?
你想打我邊度啊?
We are not allowed to collect and mop the floor.
我哋唔得開收拖地㗎都。
i won
我贏咗喇.
You won, ok.
你贏咗,ok.
Well, the poses that beauty pageants would pose nowadays, the second, third, fighting
好,選美時下會擺嘅pose, 第二、三次,fighting
time!
time!
we crossed
我 哋過左㗎喇.
Okay, you can handle it.
好好呀,你擺得啦.
You didn't participate in that beauty pageant?
你唔係參加嗰個選美呀?
no, not high enough...
冇呀,唔夠高.
And you?
你呢?
What's the matter?
呢個係咩事呀?
I'm staying hi, with your hi, hello, hi.
我stay緊hi囉,同你嗰句 hi,hello,hi.
Because many fans need two hands to lift.
因為好多fans需要兩隻手抬起.
Well, two of us have completely crossed this line this time. If you give it to you, Ah Fu...
好,我哋今次有兩個人完整過咗呢條 線㗎,分比你就,阿富哥.
Let’s talk about our character names.
講返我哋嘅角色名喇.
forgot
忘記咗喇.
A Robin Hood.
阿 羅賓漢.
I am a true man.
我即安真漢子.
That is, an honest man is like half a foot of an iceberg.
即安真漢子喇,冰山半隻腳.
Okay, it’s the second round, are you ready?
好喇,嚟到第二個回合喇,你哋 ready喇嘛?
Ready.
Ready.
Question 1, poses of prostitutes taking pictures, 1, 2, 3, fighting
第一題,大媽影相嘅pose, 1,2,3,fighting
time!
time!
very fashionable
好 fashion喎.
Because I have long legs, standing like this, people's legs will grow more.
我因為長腿喇,咁樣企呢,啲人嘅腳 會長多啲.
Such a hand is?
咁嘅手係?
beautiful
靚喎.
And you?
你呢?
I used to see prostitutes looking like this in Sai Yeung Chai South Street.
我之前喺西洋菜南街睇啲大媽咁樣.
This system...
呢個係...
lotus fish
蓮花魚喎.
I see you usually take pictures like this...
我見你平時都係咁嘅影相喎.
no it's not
唔係㗎,唔係㗎.
Okay, second question, the classic moves that have appeared in small potatoes, 1, 2, 3, fighting
好,第二題,小薯嘅出現過嘅經典動 作,1,2,3,fighting
time!
time!
What's the relationship?
呢 個係咩呀?
Get angry.
激氣喇.
The irritation is so high right?
激氣有咁高喎咩?
And Ah Bing's height is almost the same.
而阿冰嗰個高度差唔多喇.
what is this
呢個係咩嚟㗎?
This is the real one?
呢個先係真正嘅?
My lord!
本 尊!
Each type, each type of focus?
個樣,個樣重點?
You did a great job, you look like the original.
你做得好好,你好似原版喇.
You did it just like the original.
你做得好似原版喇.
almost leave
差咁啲走.
This system...
呢個係...
Beat the whip!
排鞭!
Two shots were fired successfully.
成功打兩發喇.
It's classic...
好經典喎.
I just thought of one more, this one...
我頭先仲諗到一個喇,係呢個.
It's compensation, it's compensation...
賠錢㗎,賠錢㗎.
to compensate
賠錢㗎.
Damn it, I have to pay for it, I have to pay for it...
死死,要賠錢喇,要賠錢㗎.
Wrong, your legs should be straight.
錯哂,隻腳要直㗎.
What do you want to move?
你想咩動呀?
I'm teaching him...
我教緊佢吖嘛.
Give you one chance, don't do it next time...
畀一次機會你,下次唔好喇.
Thank you very much.
多謝你呀.
What kind of material is this?
呢個咩料呀?
Your hands are so tired.
你手好疲呀.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
OK.
OK.
My hands are tired.
我嘅手好疲.
The hands are very high, so that...
手好高喎,令到.
My hands are tired...
我 嘅 手 好疲.
Question 3: Actions to attract the opposite sex.
第三題,吸引異性嘅動作.
1,2,3.
1,2,3.
It's fighting time.
It's fighting time.
Jay, what would make you think this pose is attractive to the opposite sex?
阿Jay,有啲乜嘢會令你覺得呢個 姿勢係好吸引異性㗎?
People look to high places.
人望高處吖嘛.
Looking at the sky, then you count the muscles, can you see that I'm squeezing...
望住天,跟住你又數到啲肌肉, 你都見唔見到我谷緊㗎.
To top it out like this...
要咁樣頂咗出嚟喇.
That is to say, it proves that a good waist and kidneys are a good man.
即 係證明係好腰好腎好男人喇.
First?
係咪先?
How do you think I attract heterosexuals?
你 覺得 我點樣吸引異性化喇?
Because of this, good wind dance is like this.
因為呢,好風舞係咁樣㗎.
I think dancing is very attractive when it is...
我就覺得跳舞嘅時候係好吸引嘅時候 係咯.
I don't think you are very attractive to the opposite sex.
我唔覺得你好吸引異性喇.
So kick him in the back...
咁踢佢後面啦.
No, his face is already...
唔係啊,佢個樣已經係咗.
Yes you did not make any movements did you?
係咪你冇做任何動作係咪?
He didn't make any movement.
佢冇做任何動作.
Do you know why you don't have to do anything?
知唔知點解咩都唔使做?
OK.
係囉.
I'm presenting that the most important thing to attract the opposite sex is confidence, you have to exude that confident F
我present緊吸引異性最緊要 係自信,你要散發嗰個自信嘅F
ive.
ive.
Are you ordering again?
你 又點呀?
I think he should kick in the back...
我覺得佢應該踢後面啦.
I find it very attractive.
我覺得好唔吸引.
Originally thought it was a little lower so you could look like very rich.
原本諗住係低少少可以俾你睇下好似 好有錢咁樣.
But I think it seems a little higher to show a healthy god for you to see seems better.
但我覺得好似高番少少show個健 康的神俾你睇好似好啲.
The god of health.
健康的神.
My mom met my dad after posing...
我媽咪都係擺咗pose之後就識咗 我老豆.
Your father came over there and became my wife.
你爸爸就走埋嚟嗰度做我老婆.
I think people who have a heart are the most attractive to the opposite sex...
我覺得有心事嘅人係最吸引到異性 嘅.
Movement barrel.
機心桶.
Some people say I'm in love, can you talk to me for a while?
有啲人就話我失戀啦,你可唔可以同 我傾一啲?
It's usually a man's trick.
通常係男人嘅招數嚟㗎嘛.
oh.
哦.
Have you ever done this?
你有做過啊.
I've never done it.
我 無做過.
The subject of this action is to attract the same sex.
題目呢個動作係吸引同性㗎喎.
I find that I have some misunderstandings about this question: It must be human.
我發覺我對個題目有少少誤會係咪 一定要人類啊.
Because I see stars are so attracted to the opposite sex...
因為我見到星星都係咁吸引異性啊.
Go to the back.
去後面啦.
Okay you.
好啦你.
Death.
死性.
Okay, next one.
好啦下一條啦.
The pose is scary...
嚇死人嘅姿勢吓.
1,2,3.
1,2,3.
It's my turn.
It's my turn.
Can you walk back to Chai Wan Kok Street...
你可唔可以行返去柴灣角街啦.
I am wild.
我條野.
G-man, do you think this action system is so scary? Man, do you think it is...
G-man你覺得呢個動作係好嚇死 人啊你覺得.
why?
點解?
I think it's kind of weird...
我 覺得呢個係個種奇怪嘅.
What a surprise.
好驚啊.
Good surprise.
好驚.
what is this
呢個係咩嚟㗎?
I've tried this before.
咩呢個我曾經試過.
This scared Tong Tong into flying.
咁樣嚇到彤彤飛起啊.
It scared him to go to Shenzhen...
嚇到佢去深圳㗎.
you kill us
你殺我哋啊.
Okay so this Round this is Ah B ing. And Ah J this is over the line one
好啦咁今Round呢就係阿B ing. 同埋阿J呢就過線咗一
point.
分.
good.
好.
Go to the next game immediately.
即 刻去下一個遊戲.
Action Solitaire.
動作接龍.
The first participant performs an action first.
第一位參加者先做一個動作.
The second participant will follow suit.
第二位參加者就跟住做.
Then add a new action...
然後再加上一個新嘅動作.
And so on.
如此類推.
If you fail to connect or do the wrong move, you will be eliminated.
接唔上或者做錯動作就會被淘汰.
Two people are eliminated in each round.
每個回合淘汰兩個人.
Participants who are not eliminated will get one point.
冇被淘汰嘅參加者可得一分.
Well here comes a new game.
好啦又嚟到新一個遊戲啦.
It will test your body movements and memory...
考你哋嘅形體動作同埋記性啊.
Confidence this time?
有冇信心今次?
Of course there is.
當然有囉.
The highest Q power.
最高Q力啊.
Look at Brother J doing so tightly.
睇下J哥做到咁tight.
I also know that you are a physical actor.
又知你係形體演員啦.
I think Ah J has improved a lot lately.
我覺得阿J呢排進步咗好多啊.
Because we are going to rehearsal like this Milo is playing the drums...
因為我哋呢麥羅緊鼓咁樣去彩排啊.
Milo is tight.
麥羅緊鼓啊.
I'll see what...
我睇下啲乜嘢啊.
So 4 minutes 2 times.
咁4分2次啦.
This one Drop the beat.
呢隻Drop the beat.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 heads.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 個頭啊.
What a tease.
好撩打啊.
7 8 9 10 At most, tie my neck as a gift.
7 8 9 10 最多係我個禮頸 啊.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 Two mouthfuls.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 兩口啊.
6 7 8 3 4 3 4 It's a healthy exercise...
6 7 8 3 4 3 4 健康 操嚟㗎喎.
1 2 3 4 This looks okay.
1 2 3 4 呢個樣冇事.
Some money rich...
有啲錢有錢.
7 8 9 10 1 2 3 4 Give your feet back...
7 8 9 10 1 2 3 4 畀返你腳呢.
5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 Tathagata Palm, you.
5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 如來神掌啊你.
so hard.
好難啊.
Dead.
死啦.
Every one.
個頭個頭.
Why is he twisted so softly...
點解佢扭得咁軟碎啊.
3 2 1 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1
3 2 1 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1
2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 Hahahahaha.
2 3 4 哈哈哈哈哈.
Isn't it super hard to remember?
係咪都啲超難記咪啊.
I'm starting to lose track of it.
已經開始記唔開到啦.
1 2 3 4 Sun is dead.
1 2 3 4 淽死啦.
iscal.
iscal.
Wow
嘩
I'm so noisy about your movements...
好 嘈你啲動作啊.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7, 8,9,10...
1,2,3,4,5,6,7, 8,9,10...
So pretty!
好靚呀!
Everyone is nervous...
大家攞緊張...
Wow!
嘩!
but
但
This is a movement that can come slowly. His face is keeping so calm because
呢 個係可以慢慢嚟嘅動作 佢個樣 係keep住咁calm㗎喎 因為
i thought
我 諗咗...
Here's a moment hahahaha he is a rejuvenated criminal huh!
呢邊一下 哈哈哈哈 佢係復帥犯呀 嘩!
Come to Ah J, come on Brother J!
到阿J呀 加油J哥!
left hand
左手
Grab the action yourself 4,5,6, 7,8 Wow!
自己 搶動作 4,5,6, 7,8 嘩!
It’s coming!
嚟喇!
I thought it was over!
我以為完咗呀!
6,7,8,1,2,3,4 It’s great. It’s so pretty. 5,7,
6,7,8,1,2,3,4 頂得 好好呀,頂得好靚呀 5,7,
8,1,2,3,4 Kick someone to death 5,6,7,8,1,2,3,
8,1,2,3,4 踢死人啦 5,6,7,8,1,2,3,
4 Wow!
4 嘩!
It was done!
原來係成咗!
It turns out it's done!
原來係成咗啦!
Okay, so fat mosquitoes continue. You remember those movements. After so long, fat mosquitoes will lose
好啦,咁呀肥蚊繼續 你記得哂嗰啲 動作㗎啦 隔咗咁耐咁肥蚊會輸 嚟
Hello!
囉!
5, 6,7,8 Fatty!
5, 6,7,8 肥仔!
He seems to think he can't be wrong no!
佢好似覺得自己唔會錯咁 唔係呀!
I'll keep it in mind!
我記緊呀!
Wow!
嘩!
So difficult!
咁難呀!
Crazy thread!
痴線!
is crazy
痴線㗎?
OK!
OK!
Nice one!
Nice one!
I don’t remember anymore. Just Dance!
我已經唔記得啦 Just Dance!
Yo!
Yo!
A few sounds!
幾聲喎!
Come on!
咁嚟嚟喎!
3,2,1
3,2,1
💗 are
💗 are
啱, 或 the most
啱, 或 самый
Wow!
嘩 劲嘅!!!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, every soul!
嘩,嘩 嘩 每 隻心靈!
We didn't get to... suffered!
我哋一度唔到... 受咗喇!
Damn it!
死緊喇!
So surprised!
好驚喇!
You lose!
你輸喇!
Rich brother!
富哥!
Akko!
阿可!
You lose!
你輸喇!
Rintaro is smart enough!
林太郎夠聰明喇!
Rintaro was Rintaro from the beginning to the end!
林太郎由頭到尾都係林太郎!
It's so noisy!
好嘈喎!
Throw the machine!
擲機!
Rintaro!
林太郎!
Wipe your hat on!
抹左帽喇!
Your hands are not like that, Brother Fu!
你嘅手唔係咁㗎喎,富哥!
What is it?
係咩?
Your hands are like that!
你嘅手係咁㗎喎!
Wow!
嘩!
It's so difficult!
咁難㗎!
Really don't be!
真唔好唔係嘅!
It's so difficult that I'm crazy!
難到痴咗先!
Sound is helpful!
聲音係有幫助㗎!
Buddha's Palm!
如來神掌!
Wow!
嘩!
His Tathagata Palm KOed two of them!
佢嘅如來神掌KO咗兩個!
very strong
好勁喎!
So cool!
好勁!
So we eliminated Ali Ying and Ah Bing this round!
咁我哋呢一回合就淘汰咗 阿麗英同 阿冰!
It’s so difficult for everyone!
大家都好難呀!
What a difficult game!
好難呀呢個遊戲!
It's really difficult!
真係好難!
OK!
好啦!
It’s a new round!
嚟到新一回合喇!
I hope you do some harder and more performative moves!
希望大家去做啲難啲嘅 表現性高啲 嘅動作!
We just looked down on our actions!
看唔起我哋啲動作 我哋頭先搵身解 數㗎喇!
Solve the numbers head first?
頭先解數?
So many actions!
咁多個動作!
At least step down by two!
起碼踩低兩個呀!
Dancing master!
跳舞高手!
It’s time to dance high!
擺在粒高舞啦!
Why are they not much taller than me?
點解佢哋頂無高過我好多呀?
It's not that I'm much taller than you!
唔係頂無高過你好多㗎!
I call you the income and expenditure boss!
叫你收支大仔!
Don't mess with my party!
唔好搞住我party!
DJ!
DJ!
Drop the beat!
Drop the beat!
Can't you hear what he doesn't have yet!
聽到佢無嘅啫令喎 未得啊!
The same fake move!
同一個假動作!
Didn’t get it!
未 得 啊!
Wow, it’s so difficult!
嘩好難呀!
It’s so hard to chase the wave!
好難追波呀!
OK!
OK!
Right, right, left, left, wow!
右右左左 嘩!
How good!
幾好呀!
Cross front!
十字鋒!
Wow, it’s so difficult!
嘩好難!
This...Jay is so quick!
啲呢個... 阿Jay咁快出大旋 嘅!
Twenty-character front!
廿字鋒呀!
Twenty-word front!
廿字鋒!
Very CUE, like Mr. Tang CUE.
好CUE嘅,好似唐老爺咁CUE。
No, no, it's not scary.
唔得啦,唔好吓。
Yellow label, yellow label!
黃標啦,黃標啦!
It turned out that this was difficult for him.
原來呢個都係難到佢。
So hard to follow.
好難跟。
Wow, so difficult.
嘩,好難。
I won't lose.
我唔會輸㗎。
Brother Ji, I am only 20 steps.
基哥我個係廿之步。
Not pretty I guess.
唔好靚我估啲。
Nice, so pretty.
係,好靚。
He finally went back to the real action right.
佢終於去返真正嘅動作啱啦。
Twenty steps, twenty steps, twenty steps!
廿之步,廿之步,廿之步!
But his 20th step d, not two shoot one.
但佢廿之步啲,唔係兩個拍一個㗎。
Wow, she's amazing.
嘩,佢好神奇㗎嘛。
Wow, what?
嘩, 咩嚟?
I find that looking at your face is helpful.
我發現望住你個樣係有幫助嘅。
Each action system has its own unique style.
每個動作係有得對返個樣。
How many pictures how to skip those?
幾 張點略過嗰啲啊?
Department, there are a few.
係,有少少。
It's like an ink book.
好似墨書咁啊。
You have to go on stage to perform before you have practiced dancing.
未練過舞步就要上台表演囉。
I dance well!
我跳得好啊!
Twenty steps, twenty steps, twenty steps!
廿之步,廿之步,廿之步!
Six, seven...
六、七...
Wow!
嘩!
Side first.
邊一邊先。
Then We are We are.
然後We are We are.
We are We are.
We are We are.
We are We are We are.
We are We are We are.
Michael Jackson’s Finnish!
Michael Jackson嘅 Finnish!
Wow, you talk to the chorus about Michael Jackson, you really provoke him now
嘩,你同副歌講Michael Jackson,你真係挑釁佢而家
True relationship.
真 係。
Wow, so cute!
嘩,好Cute啊!
Strange, twenty steps!
奇怪㗎,廿之步!
Really a lot of legs.
真係好多腳。
who?
係邊個?
We are We are We are We are We
We are We are We are We are We
are.
are.
So slow stuff!
咁 慢嘢!
Wow!
嘩!
big
大
Come on, don't cry, don't cry!
啲 黎,唔好哭,唔好哭!
Wow!
嘩!
Is that the line?
嘺線㗎?
What's the matter?
咩事啊?
am i me first
我係咪我先㗎?
Yes!
係呀!
Wow, please, at least yes.
嘩,請問,起碼係嘅。
Tie...
係...
I...
Yo yo...
puff?
噗?
laugh...
嘻...
You are so noisy!
好 嘈呀你!
D is just covering up the uneasiness, you understand?
啲係掩飾個不安黎㗎呢,你明唔明?
Tie?
係?
Face we all!
臉 我哋都喇!
He has to get to his own...
佢要到自己嘅.
It's me to his own...
係我到佢自己嘅.
Twenty character steps.
廿字步.
It's all 20-word steps...
全都係廿字步.
he can do it
佢做得返呀.
So cool.
勁呀.
His clothes look good...
佢嘅衣衫好好睇呀.
Do these.
做呢啲.
middle
中
ah!
呀!
I know, Brother J.
我 知呀,J哥.
I know you worked hard.
我知你好努力㗎喇.
Come on, fat mosquito.
加油,肥蚊.
Let's start sexy first.
開始sexy啲先.
Twenty character steps.
廿字步.
Is that so, Brother J, just now?
係咪咁呀,J哥,頭先?
So difficult!
好難呀!
It's like a jelly...
成個啫喱咁呀.
Wow, became a scalp guy...
嘩,變咗頭皮佬.
turned into a skin...
變 咗皮蚊咁.
What a surprise.
好驚呀.
Come on, you can...
嚟呀,你得嘅.
Twenty character steps.
廿字步.
Six seven eight one two three four.
六七八一二三四.
Five six seven eight one two three four.
五六七八一二三四.
You are a warning.
你 俾 儆 咢喎.
So surprised.
好驚喇.
Oh no
あ咩
Laugh.
笑 呀.
Wow, what a surprise.
哇,好驚呀.
It’s really hard to make AJ Guo only use the original frame.
好難做到阿J果隻原裝架其實.
Ride the bend, ride the bend, ride the bend.
騎彎,騎彎,騎彎.
Side, side, side, side.
邊呀,邊呀,邊呀,邊呀.
We are win, win, win, win.
We are win, win, win, win.
Where are you, where are you...
阿 你 喺 邊,阿你喺邊.
indivual
個
Everyone has hidden their tricks...
個 都收埋啲絕招然喇.
I hope Jumai you can dance and don't get confused...
我希望Jumai你跳到舞嘅唔好蒙 混過關.
I have to call Regus...
都係要打去列古斯打嘅.
This game is slowly evolving into a game of betting on dignity.
呢個遊戲呢,慢慢演變成賭上尊嚴嘅 遊戲喇.
You see his face, these two people's faces, changed...
你見佢個樣呢,呢兩個人個樣呢, 變咗喇.
Fortunately I I bet, 80,000 millionaire I people take 8 thousand dollars and leave even if.
好在我我賭,8萬富翁我人攞8千蚊 走咗就算啦.
Really, it's a lot of things...
真係,好搞好多嘢喇.
22...
22...
22 high.
22高.
This is really good, this...
這個真係好喇,呢個.
Hey, you dance so well.
喂,跳得好睇咗嘅.
Yes, so surprised.
係,好驚呀.
I hope it won't come...
我希望唔會到喎.
How many?
幾多個?
The most beautiful.
最靚.
1,2...
1,2...
It turns out that wrapping seems to be...
原來wrapping好似係...
undecided
冇定.
not sure
冇 定.
no can not
冇唔到.
But in GYM you will just dance strong and beautiful.
但係GYM你啱會跳得勁靚呀.
you can't lose
冇輸到㗎.
Talk about something slowly.
有事慢慢講.
In groups of two, one of them needs to guide the other to say the specified pair by acting
兩個人一組,其中一個人需要透過演 戲嘅方式,引導對方講出指定嘅對
white.
白.
Successfully speaking the assigned dialogue, both can score...
成 功講出指定嘅對白,兩個人均可 得分.
Tie.
係.
Okay, there's a new game.
好啦,有到新一個遊戲喇.
This game tests your tacit understanding and turnover...
呢個遊戲就係考你哋嘅默契同埋轉 數.
We didn't.
我哋冇.
There is no turnaround, but we can tacitly agree because we are cousins...
轉數冇,但我哋可係默契,因為係表 妹.
Ok, that's the topic...
好,個題目就係呢個.
Let's see if you can say it...
睇下你可唔可以講到喇.
good.
好.
3,2,1,action.
3,2,1,action.
Tell me something from your heart...
講一件你嘅心事嚟聽下.
my thoughts
我嘅心事...
I'm not upset.
我唔好心事.
I have something on my mind, I have something on my mind.
我有心事,我有心事.
Tell you a secret than me...
講你一個秘密比我...
You are so ugly.
你好醜樣.
Let me tell you that you know a secret better than I do.
我話講你一個秘密比我知.
I told you you are so ugly.
我話你好醜樣.
No, it's not a secret...
都唔係啊,呢個都唔係秘密.
Open secrets.
公開嘅秘密.
that cannot be concealed.
掩藏唔到嘅.
Let me tell you a secret you know better than me.
講你一個秘密比我知.
I know, I am a man.
我知,我係男人.
Come, green and red box, continue .
嚟,綠紅盒,繼續.
but i really
但我真係...
hurry up
快啲啊.
I'm willing to risk my life.
我豁出嚟喇.
Tell me your three feelings...
講你嘅三懷比我知.
I'll attack you on the street.
撲你個街啊.
What's the sentence?
係咪呢句?
Asked.
問到.
I don't dare to face it.
我唔敢面對啊.
He thought to say so like...
佢諗住講咁好似.
OK.
OK.
Can the photographer cut some?
攝影師伐啲好無?
good...
好...
Cut, cut, cut.
伐啦伐啦.
Galaxy Honey Cat talks better than me.
銀河蜜貓話比我聽啊.
I see you listen better than me.
我見你話比我聽啊.
A great achievement.
出大絕.
why did i tell you
我點解話比你聽啊.
really this
真係呢個.
Yes.
係呀.
I want to say really have to give me some applause...
我想講真係要畀啲掌聲我.
Because I am a good match.
因為 我呢一個比得好好.
Yes, I'm so nervous.
係呀,好緊張.
I really have to thank myself...
我真係要多謝我自己.
I gave this really well...
我呢個真係比得好好.
To put it bluntly, you are becoming not bad...
持平啲嚟講,你係變得唔差嘅.
This time it's Ah Fai Bin versus Ah Mosquito...
今次就係阿肥彬對阿蚊.
Fat Bintou.
肥彬頭咩.
In fact, I have already...
其實未開始我已經...
Open the teeth.
打開牙喇.
I don't know why this...
我唔知點解呢個...
First plate...
頭 盤 ...
Wear a helmet, you idiot.
戴埋頭盔你個死野.
will you beat me
你會唔會打我?
Why are you so surprised?
你做咩咁驚訝呢?
How surprising is it to hit you?
打你有幾出奇?
You know my new guy...
你識我個新漢子嚟㗎嘛.
I won't be so scared...
唔 會 咁驚呀.
I was more energetic than I was talking about.
講得我比發勁.
You look and see if you can pack it yourself.
你望一望你可唔可以咁自己一包.
So this is what Ah Fatty has to say...
咁阿肥蚊要講嘅呢就係呢一句.
OK.
OK.
3,2,1.
3,2,1.
Action.
Action.
Fat boy.
肥仔啊.
I see you always looking at me in class...
我見你喺班上面成日望住我㗎.
Why?
點解嘅?
because...
因為...
Because I only see you.
因為我只係見到你一個囉.
You are so disgusting...
你真係好噁心呀.
Not that you are wrong that you are disgusting.
唔係話你講錯話你噁心呀.
So you beat my father.
咁你打我老豆啦.
Hit me and do it.
打我做咩啫.
Hello.
喂.
Fat boy.
肥仔.
Why do I... in the morning...
點解我朝朝早...
You bought me breakfast too?
你都買早餐俾我食嘅?
You don't have enough to eat.
你唔食飽飯.
I'm not happy.
我唔安樂囉.
Hello.
喂.
You are so greasy.
好油膩呀你.
I support him...
我撐佢喎.
Achuan, you haven't been too long?
阿川你唔係過耐呀?
Because breakfast is for you.
因為 早 餐係你呀.
Let's do the same thing...
大家做返一樣嘢喎.
I don't understand that...
咁唔明呀.
I don't understand...
咁 唔 明 呀.
Yes.
係喇.
continue.
繼續.
I found a love letter in Locker before. Did you give it to me?
我之前喺Locker發現到一封情 信係咪你畀我㗎?
Absolutely.
絕對係.
because I love you.
因為我愛你.
no really good...
唔得真係好...
I really can't help it...
我真係忍唔住呀.
I'm not that COW...
我 唔係咁COW㗎.
I'm not that COW
我唔係咁COW㗎.
Are you wearing a helmet...
你戴頭盔係...
I beat him to death...
我係打死佢㗎.
I finally know why I want to be a construction worker...
我終於知道點解我要做地盤工人.
Let me think about me first...
等陣俾我諗下我先.
a bit difficult
有啲難嘅.
It's not important.
唔緊要呀.
Let me receive anything...
畀我咩都接到㗎.
I remember, I already received a love letter from you when I was in Form 1...
我記得呢,中一嘅時候我已經收過你 一封情信㗎喇.
We are all in sixth grade now...
我哋而家都中六啦.
Thank you so much.
好多謝你呀.
You will remember fondly what I wrote you.
你會好記得我寫過啲咩畀你.
Actually, Ah Bing asked this very well.
呢條其實阿冰問得好好㗎.
But the answer is so bad...
但係答得咁差嘅.
I got to that answer...
我係去到嗰個答案㗎.
really...
真係...
I told you about it myself earlier.
係 自己前面講呀.
Click, sister.
點 呀姐.
The fat intestines are so good that you can serve them right away.
肥腸好派你上即上.
I'm focused on this game.
我專注落呢個game度啦.
I can't focus on you...
我唔可以專注落你...
Did you know that many people want to sit in your seat...
你知唔知你個位係好多人想坐㗎.
That means it's been so long from Form 1 to Form 6...
即係由中一到中六都咁耐啦.
I know what you mean...
你個心意我都知㗎喇.
Actually, do you have anything to tell me...
其實你有冇啲咩想同我講呢.
I want you to be my girlfriend.
我想你做我女朋友.
right
啱呀.
But I think some of the close ones are...
但我覺得有啲近嘅都係.
I think feelings have a fight now...
我覺得感情依家有嚟搏一役.
Haven't reached his position actually...
未去到佢嗰個位呀其實.
Okay.
好喇.
stage.
個階段.
Make me complicated.
俾我複雜.
It seems like you gave him a good tip...
你好似畀佢個好好嘅提示咁喎.
oh really.
真係㗎.
Okay.
好喇.
Let him answer the last one...
畀佢答埋最後一個.
OK.
OK.
come on
嚟呀.
Send your hand first.
派你手先.
oh really?
真係㗎?
Yes.
係呀.
Send your hand first.
派你手先.
OK.
OK.
In fact, you think I'm a fan of ice?
其實你係咪當我係冰呀?
Hey hey hey hey.
喂喂喂喂.
Tie, tie, tie.
係呀係呀係呀.
Don't be like that.
唔好咁啦.
Sorry.
對唔住呀.
It's me who gave me that feeling...
係我畀咗我咁嘅感覺嚟㗎.
Okay.
好喇.
To make up for it, I didn't want to poke you at it...
為咗補償頭先唔想篤咗你一下啦.
I let Ah Bing play the drums...
我畀阿冰開鼓.
good.
好.
Ah Bing.
阿冰.
The answer is.
答案係.
Actually I've liked you for a long time...
其實我鍾意咗你好耐.
hey this is the answer
喂呢條答案嚟㗎.
this is the answer
呢 條答案嚟㗎.
The answer is really...
答案嚟㗎真係.
Okay.
好喇.
come this time
今次嚟到呀.
Li Ying and Chu Mi La...
麗瑩同埋朱咪啦.
Tie.
係.
Have confidence.
有信心啦.
have.
有.
good.
好.
This is the dialogue that Li Ying wants Chu Mi to say...
麗瑩呢要朱咪講嘅對白呢就係呢一 句.
Wow.
嘩.
okay.
好 嘅.
I can speak well to everyone.
我會講得好盡人.
You are a bad person.
好嘅.
of two.
二嘅.
I think two
我覺得二嘅.
This is two.
呢 條係二嘅.
Okay.
好喇.
Prepare.
準備.
321.
三二一.
Action.
Action.
Tell the truth.
講真.
Honestly who do I like to go out with...
講真我鍾意同邊個男女出街.
Just go out with any man or woman...
咪同邊個男女出街囉.
Actually, I don't have to care about you...
其實係唔洗理你呀.
Nice.
Nice.
Who do you think I am?
你當我係咩呀?
What do you mean?
當你係咩?
You know it yourself.
你自己知啦.
It's only justice for me to rob you of all your money, isn't it...
我搶曬你啲錢都天公地義啦係咪呀.
It's low to rob all your money...
搶曬你啲錢好低呢.
why did you lie to me
你點解要呃我?
I grabbed it in front of you...
我當住你面搶㗎喎.
You feel so stupid.
好蠢呀你個感覺.
That would make me very unhappy...
咁樣我會好唔開心㗎喎.
Yes.
係喇.
I just want you to be unhappy...
我就係想你唔開心囉.
I was with you...
我當時同你一齊嗰陣呀.
I even went out with your friend...
我仲同咗你個friend一齊出街 添呀.
Hello.
喂.
give a
畀個.
Why did you give me a cuckold?
點解你要畀綠帽我戴?
We broke up.
我哋分手.
No.
唔係喎.
break up should be now...
分左手囉應該而家.
What a weak person.
好弱呀呢個人.
What a piece of trash.
呢個垃圾.
Cheer up.
打 氣啦.
You are a bitch.
你係個八婆.
So exciting.
好勁呀.
You can get rid of this woolen hat.
呢隻帽你除得到.
You are eligible for removal.
你有資格除.
Don't be afraid of wearing it. The most important thing is to remove it quickly.
唔怕戴最緊要除得快.
So exciting.
好 勁呀.
There is a chance that I will become a loser for you.
有機會係變成你個扑街.
Or you bitch.
或者你個賤人.
You're right.
你講得中八婆.
why do you talk about bitches?
點解會講八婆嘅?
I only feel that Wumingbao is angry.
我只覺得無名寶氣之後.
You bitch.
你個八婆.
success.
成功.
really really
成 功.
what a bitch
真係八婆.
Li Ying, you are great as a bitch...
麗英你做八婆真係好出色.
yes honey.
係嘅.
Make a play.
做戲啫.
Make fun of everyone.
做 戲啫大家.
Li Ying, you are always right...
麗英你成日咁啱嘅.
Yes.
係喇.
so just right
咁啱啱嘅.
I really don't know why that's right...
真 係唔知點解咁啱喎.
good.
好.
Next group.
下一組.
The next White House.
下一個白宮.
Okay.
好喇.
Here comes a new group...
嚟到新一組喇.
That's Ah J...
就係阿J喇.
So just now Ah Bing couldn't get points...
咁剛才阿冰拎唔到分啦.
So I sent Ah Bing to confront you.
所以就派阿冰同你對喇.
I didn't get any points just yet...
我啱啱都拎唔到分㗎.
Department La.
係 喇.
Although I've known you for ten years...
雖然同你識咗十年.
but no
但係冇啊.
That is, my feelings for Ah Bing...
即係我對阿冰嘅.
I'm with you.
我係你.
I did the same to you...
我都係咁樣對你嘅.
good.
好.
What about Ah J.
咁阿J呢.
This is the sentence for Ah Bing to say...
要阿冰講嘅句子呢就係呢一句.
it doesn't make sense anymore...
都冇make sense喇.
So nervous.
緊張呀.
It seems hard to say and it seems far away.
好似好難講又好似好遠喎.
Then you might not have to talk...
咁就可能唔使講嘢嘅.
oh really?
真係㗎?
Very much looking forward to it.
好期待喇.
Prepare.
準備.
three.
三.
two.
二.
one.
一.
Action.
Action.
don't walk around
唔好行埋嚟.
Ah J, don't get any closer.
阿J你唔好越嚟越近喎.
it's hard to do
好難做㗎.
Please come a little farther from me...
請你嚟我遠一點.
How am I stylish today?
我今日有型咩?
Brother J, you are so handsome.
J哥你好型呀.
Brother J, can you be so cool?
J哥你咁型得唔得㗎?
Is it really that cool...
其實係唔係真咁型嘅.
dumb.
啞.
Is he dumb?
啞咩呀佢?
Brother J, you are so strange.
J哥你好奇怪呀.
Brother J...
J哥...
Order it?
點呀?
I...
我...
How stupid.
好蠢呀.
Brother J, aren't you feeling unwell?
J哥你唔係唔舒服呀?
Say it's not uncomfortable?
話唔係唔舒服?
Brother J, you are a pervert.
J哥你係變態佬.
Brother J, you are so wretched.
J哥你好猥瑣呀.
Neurosis.
神 經 病 呀.
Brother J, you are so bad.
J哥你好樣衰.
Hello brother J...
J哥你好...
Electric stalk.
電梗.
It hurts so much.
好心痛呀.
It's really Shanghai all the time...
真係下下都上海啦.
You are not heavy enough.
你都唔夠重呀.
Hello brother J...
J哥你好...
Quter.
屈特.
There are some pianos...
有啲琴呀.
Go away.
走開.
Actually, Ah Bing is miserable to some extent...
其實阿冰係某程度上係慘嘅.
Say the words inside you...
講你身入面嗰句.
I think...
我覺得...
I like you so much.
我好鍾意你呀.
What do you think?
你覺得點呀?
I think...
我覺得...
I feel uncomfortable.
我覺得唔舒服呀.
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
有咩唔舒服呀?
what is it
係乜嘢呀?
it's over
完 咗喇.
OK, J.
好,阿J.
What is that saying?
講嗰句嘢係咩呀?
I feel like vomiting when I see you.
我見到你想嘔呀.
Do you ever feel this way?
你有冇有呢種感覺呀?
I do not have it.
我冇呀.
he didn't
佢冇呀.
Actually, I feel so awake.
其實好醒呀.
That is happy he couldn't say that sentence...
即 係開心嘅佢講唔到嗰句說話.
You are so awake.
你好醒呀.
I just counted him buried...
我 頭先你計佢埋埋呢.
The look between you and Ah Bing lasted for more than two minutes...
你同阿冰嘅對望超過兩分鐘.
Yeah, this is the only time I can look at each other up close.
係呀,我唯一一次可以近距離對望.
Okay.
好喇.
Anyway.
Anyway啦.
So on this one you both are the same no points.
咁就呢一番你哋兩個一樣都係冇分.
save you.
救你.
Excited.
激氣.
Okay.
好喇.
We have finished playing the three theater mini-games...
我哋玩完三個劇場嘅小遊戲喇.
As a result, four people got the same score.
結果呢就有四位同分喇.
That means there are four losers...
即係有四位係輸家嘅.
The difference is...
分別就係.
Li Ying, Ah J, Ah Bing, and Ju Mi.
禮英,阿J,阿冰,同埋朱咪.
We are already standing in a group.
我哋已經站埋一組喇.
Ah J, congratulations.
阿J,恭喜你喇.
And this position is not perfect.
又 善唔完呢個位.
Congratulations.
恭喜你喇.
You don't have to lose as a host...
你做主持人唔使輸.
come here everyone
過嚟喇大家.
Behead, behead.
斬殺,斬殺.
Finished playing with the three CAMs.
玩完呢三隻CAM.
Do you think it was helpful for our show?
覺得對我哋嗰個show有冇幫助 呢?
of course there is
梗係有喇.
We just lined up a dance right...
我哋啱啱排咗隻舞吖嘛.
If you want to see it, we'll jump back to the show...
如果大家想睇,我哋會喺個show 跳返喇.
Nothing wrong.
無錯.
We have click HAM, choreography instructor milk tea work.
我哋有撳HAM,排舞導師奶茶嘅 工作喇.
Then we will also tell milk tea, milk tea we help you sort very unreasonable.
跟住我哋仲會同奶茶講, 奶茶我哋 幫你排好無理嘅.
I think he is going to say that this dance is not my line...
我覺得佢係要納外講話, 呢隻舞唔 係我排呀.
Plea him guilty, do you know...
認罪佢㗎知唔知.
Finally, thank you to Edward Chung for letting us shoot the Party Game here.
最後多謝命愛華德中 畀我哋喺呢度 拍Party Game呀.
You are such a hostage...
你真係好人質呀.
Okay,3,2,1.
好喇,3,2,1.
Xue Jie Party Game, jump back to your sister Xue Jie.
雪姐Party Game, 跳返你姐雪姐.
Okay, rowing.
好,排野.
All together, all together, all together, all together.
齊齊,齊齊,齊齊,齊齊.
Low platform, suitable for me.
低 台,適合我.
All together.
齊齊.